## Pitchayakit Pahamak Software Engineer

Last update: July 22, 2022

The online version is available at

https://pitchayakit.github.io/cv

#### Residence

Bangkok, Thailand

#### **Phone**

**\** +66831225471

#### **GitHub**

pitchayakit

#### **Email**

☑ pitchayakit.p@gmail.com

```
Laravel
++++
PHP
++++
Livewire
++++
Bootstrap
++++
Tailwind
++++

AlpineJs
++++
jQuery
++++
Restful
++++
GIT
++++
SQL
++++

VueJs
+++
NodeJs
+++
Python
++
```

Over 6 years of software development career in a variety of companies including startup and digital agency. I graduated with a Master's degree in Network Learning Technology, NCU, Taiwan. I has been working on both back-end and front-end website development. Moreover, I am intersted in IoT and Machine learning. Please get in touch.

## **Professional Experience**

#### Lexicon

2020 - Present

- Managed up Line CRM system
- Managed up CMS using Laravel, Nova, and WordPress
- Electric search
- Data migration
- Coaching junior developer in web development and technical support



#### Freelancer

2018 - 2020

- Managed up to 5 company websites
- Managed up to 2 E-commerce websites
- 1 library website for searching books using Laravel

| WordPress | Laravel

## **Empag**

2017 - 2018

- Coaching internships in web development and technical support
- Managed up to 4 web content management systems and tasks at a given time
- Collaborate with designer in order to ensure quality and accuracy of the designy
- A Support tool for web scraping and export to excel file

WordPress NodeJs

#### Onestockhome

Mar 2017 – Sep 2017

• Migration content management system to Ruby on Rail platform

- Developed front-end website using jQuery, Boostrap, HTML and CSS in Ruby on Rail platform
- Supported the use of content management system and improve user interface

Ruby on Rail React

### Rippleworkz

2016 - 2017

- Integrated HTML to WordPress and Prestashop
- Managed up to 4 webs content management system and tasks at a given time.
- Collaborate with project manager to develop website, which is beyond own management project

WordPress JQuery

# SeSaMe (Sensor-enhanced Social Media) Center, National University of Singapore

Jul 2015 - Dec 2015

- SENSE video analytics web application replaced video output for detection, tracking and counting by HTML Canvas
- Take over and developed SeSaMe website using Joomla CMS

Play Framework | HTML Canvas | Joomla | OpenCV | MongoDB

#### **Education**

Master of Network Learning Technology, College of Electrical Engineering & Computer Science, National Central University, Taiwan [2018 - 2020]

Bachelor of Computer Engineering, College of Engineering, Kasetsart University, Thailand [2013 - 2016]

## **Additional Experience**

A Study of using IoT and Zenbo robot to facilitate students' interaction in flipped classroom and the analysis of their perception.

[IoT] Zenbo] Machine learning

Smart home with door and light control System.

IoT PHP JQuery